<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<newsList>

<news > 
<title> Professor Liangcheng Tu give a talk</title>
<image>./images/activity/Tuliang Cheng_20180604.jpg </image> 
<text> On June 4-5, 2018, invited by Prof. Jiang, Prof. Liangcheng Tu from Huazhong University of Science and Technology gave a talk about "Astroobservation and Geodeticsurvey". This report mainly introduced the "TIANQIN mission". The main content is the method of measuring gravitational waves.</text> 
<time> 2018-6-4 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> Professor Yue Zhang give a talk</title>
<image>./images/activity/Zhangyue_20180525.jpg </image> 
<text> On May 25-26, 2018，invited by Prof. Jiang, Prof. Yue Zhang from University of Leicester gave a talk about "the 2020 5G-PPP Phase2 project of the EU horizon: Internet of Radio Light (IoRL)". The talk mainly introduced the long distance radio head system based on 5G millimeter wave system, which can be effectively integrated into various types of LED intelligent lighting systems.  A wireless optical front-end device, an adaptive high efficiency transmission technology and an intelligent software definition network which can be integrated into LED lighting system are designed.
  </text> 
<time> 2018-5-25 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title>  Doctor's thesis defense in 2018 </title>
<image>./images/activity/Nichunxing_20180202.jpg </image> 
<text> On February 2-3, 2018, Ni Chunxing defended the Doctor's thesis.</text> 
<time> 2018-02-02 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> Workshop on Artificial Intelligence Aided Solutions for Complex Problems in Communications</title>
<image>./images/activity/AI_20170817.jpg</image> 
<text> On August 17-19, 2017, "Workshop on Artificial Intelligence Aided Solutions for Complex Problems in Communications" was held at Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics (WNLO). Enhong Chen (Professor from University of Science and Technology of China), Shi Jin (Professor from Southeast University), Feifei Gao (Professor from Tsinghua University), Xiaohu Tang (Professor from Southwest Jiao Tong University), Xin Wang (Professor from Fudan University) as well as Associate Professor Kai Luo, Dr. Da Chen, Dr. Yuzhou Li, Dr. Yang Cao in our lab gave talks. Professor Enhong Chen introduced the analysis and application of big data and emphasized the importance of big data in the development of artificial intelligence. Professor Shi Jin introduced the basis of artificial intelligence and 5G wireless transmission, and indicated that artificial intelligence can be applied in 5G communication. Professor Feifei Gao introduced array signal processing and wireless communication in Massive MIMO and proposed a wireless communication method based on array signal processing. Professor Xiaohu Tang introduced the storage and computing vehicle network -- Mobile Edge network and proposed the feasibility of wireless communication based on storage. Professor Xin Wang proposed a low latency and efficient wireless resource allocation method based on statistical learning. Associate professor Kai Luo introduced the application of multicarrier in waveform design of radar communication. Dr. Da Chen introduced the tradeoff between the spectral characteristics of the multi carrier signal and the channel estimation performance. Dr. Yuzhou Li introduced the positioning and navigation of autonomous underwater vehicle. Dr. Yang Cao introduced cooperative video processing on the mobile edge for multimedia IOT applications.  </text> 
<time> 2017-08-17 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> Academician of Chinese Academy of Engineering Quan Yu Visited Our Lab</title>
<image>./images/activity/Yuquan_20170723.jpg</image> 
<text> On July 22-24, 2017, invited by Prof. Jiang, Prof. Quan Yu, who is an Academician of Chinese Academy of Engineering, visited our lab. Faculty members in our lab gave talks about FBMC, Polar code, heterogeneous networks, and so on. Prof. Yu and the members in our lab held an in-depth discussion about these topics.  </text> 
<time> 2017-07-23 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> The Acceptance Inspection of a National 863 Project </title>
<image>./images/activity/National863_Project_20170717.jpg</image> 
<text> On July 15-17, 2017, the acceptance inspection of our National 863 Project, "New-type Coding/Decoding and Modulation/De-modulation Techniques for 5G Wireless Communications Systems" (2015AA01A710), was held at Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics (WNLO). Yaowei Fu (director of the High Technology Research and Development Center of the Ministry of Science and Technology), Hong Xiang (project director), Xiaohu You (professor from the Southeast University), Hua Yang (TD Industry Alliance Secretary General), Zhiqin Wang (president of the Ministry of information industry and Telecommunications Research Institute), Fusheng Zhu (wireless product director in ZTE), Fengyi Yang (Professor from the China Telecom Group Ltd. Beijing Research Institute), Yang Yang (researcher from Shanghai radio communication research center), Guangyong Zhou (deputy director in the science development of our school) and representatives from each cooperative organization attended the meeting. Prof. Tao Jiang gave a report on the research results. The expert group inspected the FBMC-CoMP hardware test platform set up. After discussion, the expert group put forward the acceptance opinions and agreed to accept the project. </text> 
<time> 2017-07-17 </time>
</news>


<news > 
<title> Prof. Xinyu Zhang Gave a Talk </title>
<image>./images/activity/Xinyu_Zhang_20170707.jpg </image> 
<text> On July 7-8, 2017, Prof. Xinyu Zhang from Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering at the University of Wisconsin-Madison gave a talk about "Designing the Wireless Internet of Things with Ambient Awareness". The talk mainly introduced two critical underpinnings for IoT: (i) wireless network architectures that can scale to billions of devices with wire-speed connectivity; (ii) ubiquitous sensing mechanisms that enable the devices to be aware of ambient locations and micro-activities. In addition, Prof. Zhang shared the experience of doing research on fields of Network MIMO, IoT, Smart Sensing, MIMO, System Design and so on. </text> 
<time> 2017-07-07 </time>
</news>


<news > 
<title>  Doctor's thesis defense in 2017 </title>
<image>./images/activity/Salman_Saadat_20170513.jpg </image> 
<text> On May 13-14, 2017, Salman Saadat defended the Doctor's thesis.</text> 
<time> 2017-05-13 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> Dr. Yong Li Gave a Talk</title>
<image> ./images/activity/YongLi_20170409.jpg</image> 
<text> On April 9-10, 2017, Dr. Yong Li from Tsinghua University gave a talk, "Understanding the Cyber-Physical Space by Mobile Operator Big Data". The report mainly introduced how to analyze people’s social behavior. The methods are based on current mobile networks, urban management, and robust cycber-physical systems.</text> 
<time> 2017-04-09 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> The East Lake International Forum for Outstanding Overseas Young Scholars in 2016</title>
<image> ./images/activity/EastLakeForum_20161227.jpg</image> 
<text> On December 27-29, 2016, "The East Lake International Forum for Outstanding Overseas Young Scholars in 2016" was held in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics (WNLO). Dr. Hongzhi Guo from the State University of New York at Buffalo, Dr. Yue Cao from Northumbria University, Dr. Lei Zhang from the University of Surrey, Dr. Peng Wang from Huawei Swedish Institute, Dr. Xiaohu Fang from the Chinese University of Hong Kong, and Dr. Mingjie Feng from the Auburn University attended the forum and gave wonderful talks. </text> 
<time> 2016-12-27 </time>
</news>

<news > 
<title> Dr. Yong Xiao gave a talk</title>
<image> </image> 
<text> On December 24-25, 2016, Prof. Jiang invited Yong Xiao (Assistant professor from the University of Arizona) to give a wonderful talk "Quality-of-Experience (QoE) and Power Efficiency Tradeoff for Fog Computing Networks" in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics (WNLO). The report introduced two important performance metrics for fog computing networks: quality-of-experience (QoE) and power efficiency. A fundamental tradeoff between QoE and power efficiency was also discussed.</text> 
<time> 2016-12-24 </time>
</news>


<news > 
<title> 2016 IEEE Global Communications Conference (GLOBECOM)</title>
<image> </image> 
<text> On December 4–9, 2016, Prof. Tao Jiang, Prof. Wei Wang, PhD students Hao Zhu and Boxi Liu attended the 2016 IEEE Global Communications Conference (GLOBECOM) in Washington, D.C., USA. Hao Zhu gave an academic report "Energy-Aware Incentive Mechanism for Content Sharing Through Device-to-Device Communications". On Professor Daiming Qu's behalf, Hao Zhu also gave an academic report "Finer SVD-based Beamforming for FBMC/OQAM systems".</text> 
<time> 2016-12-08 </time>
</news>


<news > 
<title>  President of IEEE VTS Javier Gozalvez gave a talk</title>
<image>./images/activity/Javier Gozalvez_report_20161022.jpg </image> 
<text> On October 20-21, 2016, President of the IEEE Vehicular Technology Society (IEEE VTS) Javier Gozalvez, Universidad Miguel Hernández de Elche (UMH), gave a wonderful talk "Device-centric Wireless Networking for 5G" in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics (WNLO). He mainly discussed three aspects: the potential of device-centric wireless technologies to improve energy efficiency, quality of service and capacity compared to conventional base station-centric cellular communications.</text> 
<time> 2016-10-20 </time> 
</news>


<news > 
<title> Doctor's thesis defense </title> 
<image>./images/activity/doctordefense2016.jpg </image> 
<text> On June 17-18, 2016, Dejin Kong and Mohammed Qasim Mohammed Sulttan defended their Doctor's thesis.  </text> 
<time> 2016-06-17 </time> 
</news>


<news > 
<title> Master's thesis defense </title> 
<image>./images/activity/by2016q.jpg</image> 
<text> On May 22-23, 2016, Master's thesis defense was taken place.</text> 
<time> 2016-05-22 </time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> 2016 Innovation Symposium on Wireless Communications  </title> 
<image>./images/activity/psbq.jpg</image> 
<text> On April 5-10, 2016, the forum of "2016 Innovation Symposium on Wireless Communications" was held in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics (WNLO). The forum was hosted by Prof. Tao Jiang. The topics focused on the new technologies of wireless communications. The president Lieyun Ding of Huazhong University of Science and Technology delivered a speech for the forum. Party secretary Song Xia of WNLO, Prof. Shaoqian Li from University of Electronic Science and Technology, Prof. Guo Wei from University of Science and Technology, Prof. Fuchun Zheng from SouthEast University, Prof. Hongbo Zhu from Nanjing Post and Communications University, Prof. Xiaohu Tang from South West JiaoTong University, other 50 experts and scholars, teachers and students from WNLO took part in the forum. </text> 
<time> 2016-04-05 </time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Yu-Dong Yao gave a talk</title> 
<image>./images/activity/yaoyudong.jpg</image> 
<text>Invited by Prof. Jiang, Prof. Yu-Dong Yao from Stevens Institute of Technology visited conference hall of School of Electronic Information and Communications on June 15, 2015, and gave a wonderful talk with title of "Cognitive Radio Research: Spectrum Sensing and Identification of Radio Terminals and Malicious Users". </text> 
<time> 2015-06-15 </time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> Optical communications Collaborative Innovation Forum </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 12-17, 2015, "Optical communications Collaborative Innovation Forum" was held in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Party secretary Song Xia delivered a speech for the forum. Prof. Jiang chaired the forum named "Optical Communication Industry and Technology". Academician Zisen Zhao, academician Zhongliang Zhu, Prof. Xiaoping Zheng from Tsinghua University, Principal Shaohua Yu from WRI, Prof. Zhengyuan Xu from University of Science and Technology of China, Prof. Jianjun Yu from Fudan University, Prof. Lianshan Yan from SouthWest JiaoTong University, Prof. Gangxiang Shen from Suzhou University, Prof. Guifang Li from Tianjin University, Prof. Chen Gong from University of Science and Technology of China, Prof. Yikai Su from Shanghai JiaoTong University, Prof. Xiangjun Xin from Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications, Prof. Yulong Zou from Nanjing University of Posts and Telecommunications, and Dr. Qi Yang from WRI attended the forum.</text> 
<time> 2015-06-12 </time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Prof. Chao-kai Wen and Prof. Shi Jin visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On March 21-24, 2015, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Chao-kai Wen from Taiwan National Sun Yat-sen University and Prof. Shi Jin from the Southeast University to visit our laboratory. Prof. Wen gave a seminar about his recent research on joint channel estimation and data detection based on low-accuracy analog to digital converter. Then a deep discussion about the Massive MIMO research problems was held.   </text> 
<time> 2015-03-21 </time> 
</news>




<news> 
<title>2014 The New Technologies of Wireless Communication</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On January 14-19, 2015, Prof. Jiang invited 7 specialists and scholars to attend the workshop of "2014 The New Technologies of Wireless Communication". Prof. Wei Chen from Tsinghua University, Prof. Hongkai Xiong from Shanghai Jiaotong University, Prof. Lingyang Song from Peking University and Prof. Shi Jin from Southeast University gave academic reports. </text> 
<time> 2015-01-14 </time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Prof. Zhiquan Luo gave a talk </title>
<image>  </image> 
<text> On September 19-20, 2014, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Zhiquan Luo from University of Minnesota to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics and give a wonderful talk "Optimal Joint Provision of Backhaul and Radio Access Networks".  </text> 
<time> 2014-09-19 </time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> Prof. Shiwen Mao gave a talk </title>
<image>  </image>
<text> On July 10-11, 2014, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Shiwen Mao from Auburn University to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics and give a wonderful talk "On Video Streaming in Cognitive Femtocell Networks". </text> 
<time> 2014-07-10 </time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Qian Zhang gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 27-28, 2014, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Qian Zhang from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics and give a wonderful talk "Efficient and Reliable Design for Extremely Dense Wireless Networks".   </text> 
<time> 2014-06-27 </time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> 2013 WCSP </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On October 24–27, 2013, Prof. Tao Jiang, Associate Professor Wei Peng and Doctor Liang Yu attended the 2013 International Conference on Wireless Communications and Signal Processing (WCSP) in Hangzhou. Associate Professor Wei Peng gave an academic report "Analysis on the Transmission Delay of Priority-Based Secondary Users in Cognitive Radio Networks". Dr. Liang Yu gave an academic report "Risk-constrained Operation for Internet Data Centers under Smart Grid Environment".  </text> 
<time> 2013-10-24</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> The 2nd session of "The New Technologies of Wireless Communication" </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On October 20-24, 2013, the 2nd session of "The New Technologies of Wireless Communication" was held in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. More than 10 specialists and scholars attended the workshop. Prof. Tao Jiang presided over the opening ceremony. Prof. Xuemin Shen from Univ. of Waterloo, Prof. Nei Kato, from Tohoku University, Prof. Junshan Zhang from Arizona State Univ., Prof. Susan Cheng from George Washington Univ., Prof. Yu Cheng from Illinois Institute of Tech., gave talks on their research. </text> 
<time> 2013-10-20</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title>  Progress report of National Basic Research Program of China (973 Program) </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On August 26-27, 2013, members of the project supported by the National Basic Research Program of China (973 Program) from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Tsinghua University, Huazhong University of Science and Technology gave a report on the progress of preliminary works in Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Xiwen Liu from Huazhong University of Science and Technology, Kaishun Wu, Yanjiao Chen from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Shaoyang Li, Yipeng Sun and Yang Li from Tsinghua University gave the talk. Ning Ge from Tsinghua University introduced the whole situation of project. </text> 
<time> 2013-08-26</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Prof. Junshan Zhang visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On August 2-4, 2013, Prof. Junshan Zhang from Arizona State Univ., invited by the QoE Oriented Collaborative Computing Communication Theory Research Group, came to Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics for a three-day academic exchange.  </text> 
<time> 2013-08-02</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> 2013 IEEE Forum on Media Computing and Communication </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 22-23, 2013, Prof.Tao Jiang and Xiwen Liu attended the 2013 IEEE Forum on Media Computing and Communication in Xidian University. They listened to the report of the newest research and had a deep exchange with the experts on related research.  </text> 
<time> 2013-07-22</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Professor Qian Zhang visited our lab </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 9-11, 2013, Professor Qian Zhang from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, invited by the QoE Oriented Collaborative Computing Communication Theory Research Group, came to Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics for a three-day academic exchange.  </text> 
<time> 2013-07-09</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Half-yearly meeting of the 973 Program </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text>  On June 28-30, 2013, Prof. Daiming Qu, Dr. Lei Zhang, and Master Xiwen Liu attended half-yearly meeting of the 973 Program in Tsinghua University. Then reported the process report of the research and inquired into the future work.   </text> 
<time> 2013-06-30</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title>  International Workshop on Mathematical Issues in Information Sciences </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> From June 29 to July 5, 2013, Dr. Yang Zhou, Liang Yu, Chunxing Ni and others attended the International Workshop on Mathematical Issues in Information Sciences in Xidian University. </text> 
<time> 2013-06-29</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Professor Pingyi Fan, Yuan Luo and Xiangming Li visited our lab </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 23-25, 2013, Prof.Pingyi Fan from Tsinghua University, Prof. Yuan Luo from Shanghai Jiaotong University, Prof.Xiangming Li from Beijing Institute of Technology, invited by the QoE Oriented Collaborative Computing Communication Theory Research Group, came to Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics for academic exchange. </text> 
<time> 2013-06-24</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Dapeng Wu gave a talk </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On May 16-18, 2013, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Dapeng Wu from University of Florida to visite Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Prof. Dapeng Wu gave a wonderful talk "Energy-Efficient Scheduling Policy for Collaborative Execution in Mobile Cloud Computing". </text> 
<time> 2013-05-16</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Course on "Convex Optimization and its Applications"</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On May 6-25, 2013, Yang Zhou, Wenjie Jia, Xusheng Xiong, Fei Li, Jun Li and Deying Kong attended a tentative course about "Convex Optimization and its Applications", which was organized by Professor Zhi-Quan Luo, in Xi'an. </text> 
<time> 2013-05-06</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> 2013 IEEE Wireless Communications And Networking Conference </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On April 7-12, 2013, Prof. Jiang, Zhou Yang, Dejin Kong, Wenjie Jia, Chunxing Ni, Huaqing Zhang, Jingkai Wu, Xusheng Xiong, Sha Meng attended the 2013 IEEE Wireless Communications And Networking Conference in Shanghai. Huaqing Zhang delivered oral presentations "On the Interference Avoidance Method in Two-tier LTE Networks with Femtocells". Dejin Kong delivered oral presentations "Frequency Domain Averaging for Channel Estimation in OQAM-OFDM Systems". </text> 
<time> 2013-04-07</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Workshop on The New Technologies of Wireless Communication </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On November 28-30, 2012, Prof. Jiang invited more than 20 specialists and scholars in the field of wireless communication technology to the workshop "The New Technologies of Wireless Communication". Prof. Xiaohu You from Southeast University gave a wonderful talk "The Future Development Direction-Cellular Mobile Communication". Prof. Shaoqian Li from University of Electronic Science and Technology gave a wonderful talk "The Opportunities and Challenges of Wireless Communication". Prof. Zhisheng Niu from Tsinghua University gave a wonderful talk "The New Architecture in Super Cellular Network for 5G". Prof. Hongke Zhang from Beijing Jiaotong University gave a wonderful talk "The Present Situation and Facing Problems of the Internet Technology". Prof. Tao Jiang from Huazhong University of Science and Technology gave a wonderful speech "Continuously Improve Spectrum Efficiency of Broadband Wireless Communication".  </text> 
<time> 2012-11-30</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> The 3rd IEEE International Conference on Smart Grid Communications  </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text>  On November 5-9, 2012, Prof. Jiang and Liang Yu have attended the 3rd IEEE International Conference on Smart Grid Communications, Tainan, Taiwan, China. Liang Yu delivered oral presentations "Risk Management in Internet Data Center Operations under Smart Grid Environment" and "Multiple Resource Expansion Planning in Smart Grids with High Penetration of Renewable Generation".  </text> 
<time> 2012-11-05</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Dr. Yong Xiao gave a lecture</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On November 3-4, 2012, Prof. Jiang invited Dr. Yong Xiao from Nanyang Technological University to visit Wuhan National Laboratory. Dr. Yong Xiao gave a wonderful talk "Distributed Optimization for Cognitive Radio Networks Using Game Theory".  </text> 
<time> 2012-11-03</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Ying-Chang Liang gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On October 26-27, 2012, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Ying-Chang Liang from the Institute for Infocomm Research, A*STAR to visit Wuhan National Laboratory. Prof. Ying-Chang Liang gave a wonderful talk "Random matrix theory, large scale MIMO, and cognitive radio".  </text> 
<time> 2012-10-26</time> 
</news>




<news> 
<title> IEEE International Conference on Communications in China </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On August 15-18, 2012, Lei Zhang, Mingjie Feng, Dejin Kong and Chunxing Ni attended the first IEEE International Conference on Communications in China(ICCC), Beijing, China.  </text> 
<time> 2012-08-15</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Junshan Zhang gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On August 3-4 2012, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Junshan Zhang from the EE Department at Arizona State University to visit Wuhan National Laboratory. Prof. Junshan Zhang gave a wonderful talk "A Note on Emerging Science for Interdependent Networks".  </text> 
<time> 2012-08-03</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> International Workshop on Mathematical Issues in Information Sciences </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 7-14, 2012, Prof. Jiang, Zhongnian Li, Zhiqiang Wang, Lei Zhang, Chi Cheng, Liang Yu, Qibiao Zhu, Mingjie Feng, Dejin Kong, Chunxing Ni and Xiwen Liu attended the International Workshop on Mathematical Issues in Information Sciences, Xi'an, China.  </text> 
<time> 2012-07-07</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> Prof. Jiang gave a lecture in Hubei University of Technolog</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 4-5, 2012, Prof. Jiang visited Hubei University of Technology and gave a talk "Hot Topics and Directions in Efficient and Secure Broadband Wireless Communication Networks". </text> 
<time> 2012-06-04</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Course on "Advanced Optimization Methods" </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> From May 21 to June 2, 2012, Dejin Kong and Chunxing Ni attended a tentative course "Advanced Optimization Methods", which was organized by Professor Zhi-Quan Luo in Xi'an.  </text> 
<time> 2012-05-21</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Dapeng Wu gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On May 28-29, 2012, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Dapeng Wu from University of Florida to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Prof. Dapeng Wu gave a wonderful talk "Identication of Network Dynamics and Its Applications".  </text> 
<time> 2012-05-28</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> 2011 Annual Summing-up Meeting  </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On December 25-26, 2011, Yang Cao was offered the first-class scholarships, Da Chen, Mingjie Feng and Dejin Kong were offered the second-class scholarships, Cai Li, Chang Xu, Liang Yu and Li Li were offered the third-class scholarships at the annual summing-up meeting. </text> 
<time> 2011-12-25</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> IEEE GLOBECOM 2011 </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On December 5-11, 2011, Prof. Jiang, Yang Cao, Yang Zhou and Liang Yu have attended the IEEE GLOBECOM 2011, Houston, Texas, USA. Liang Yu and Yang Cao delivered oral presentations "Improving Achievable Traffic Load of Secondary Users Under GoS Constraints in Cognitive Wireless Networks" and "Novel Navigation Algorithm for Wireless Sensor Networks Without Information of Locations", respectively. </text> 
<time> 2011-12-05</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> The International Photonics and OptoElectronics Meetings 2011</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On November 2-6, 2011, the International Photonics and OptoElectronics Meetings (POEM) 2011 has been held in Wuhan science and technology exhibition center, Wuhan, China. Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Richard Penty, Dr. Changyuan Yu, Prof. Lianshan Yan, Prof. Chester Shu, Prof. Xiaoping Zheng, Prof. Gangxiang Shen, Prof. Ping Kong Alexander Wai, Prof. Chunming Qiao, Dr. Sugang Xu, Prof. Yikai Su, Dr. Qi Yang and Dr. Xu Wang to give wonderful presentations on the session of Optical Communication Systems and Networking (OSCN).</text> 
<time> 2011-11-02</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Dr Ying-Chang Liang gave a talk </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On October 17-18, 2011, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Yingchang Liang from Singapore Institute for Infocomm Research (I2R) to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Prof. Yingchang Liang gave a wonderful talk "Cognitive Radio Networks: The Reality and the Road Ahead". </text> 
<time> 2011-10-17</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Qian Zhang gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On September 23-24, 2011, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Qian Zhang from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Prof. Qian Zhang gave a wonderful talk "Subcarrier Coding: A Fast Coordination Approach in Cognitive Radio Networks". </text> 
<time> 2011-09-23</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Yang Cao awarded 2011 MSRA Fellowship </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On September 9-10, 2011, Yang Cao awarded 2011 MSRA Fellowship. This year, 102 distinguished Ph.D. candidates from 42 leading research universities/institutions were nominated for fellowships. Applicants included candidates from the Chinese mainland, Hong Kong, Taiwan, Australia, Japan, South Korea and Singapore.  </text> 
<time> 2011-09-09</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title>Prof. Andrea Goldsmith gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On August 17-18, 2011, Prof. Jiang invited Prof. Andrea Goldsmith from Stanford University to visit Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics. Prof. Andrea Goldsmith gave a wonderful talk "The Road Ahead for Wireless Technology: Dreams and Challenges". </text> 
<time> 2011-08-17</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> The IEEE INFOCOM 2011 </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On April 9-16, 2011, Prof. Jiang and 4 PhD students, Chi Cheng, Yang Cao, Lei Zhang and Liang Yu attended IEEE INFOCOM 2011, Shanghai. INFOCOM is one top conference in the area of networks, which attracts more than 1000 attendees every year.  </text> 
<time> 2011-04-09</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Doctorate dissertation proposal </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On January 8-9, 2011, Prof. Honggang Zhang from Zhejiang University and Prof. Changchuan Yin from Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications visited our laboratory. They joined our doctorate dissertation proposal and gave many valuable suggestions for our research.  </text> 
<time> 2011-01-08</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> 2010 Annual Summing-up Meeting  </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On December 30-31, 2010, Zhiqiang Wang and Jie Ding were offered the first-class scholarship, while Chi Cheng and Lili Guan were offered the second-class scholarship at the annual summing-up meeting.  </text> 
<time> 2010-12-30</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> The IEEE GLOBECOM 2010 </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On December 6-11, 2010, Prof. Jiang and Jie Ding attended IEEE GLOBECOM 2010 held in Miami.  </text> 
<time> 2010-12-06</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title>  Workshop on New Directions in Wireless Communications and Networking   </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 9-12, 2010, Prof. Zhisheng Niu from Tsinghua University invited Prof. Jiang to attend the "Special Workshop on New Directions in Wireless Communications and Networking". Prof. P. R. Kumar, Prof. Jehoshua Bruck, Prof. Lang Tong, Prof. Lajos hanzo, Prof. Soung-Chang Liew, Prof. Xiaodong Wang, Prof. Dapeng Wu, Prof. Devavrat Shah, Prof. Shuguang Cui, Prof. Qianchuan Zhao, Prof. Ada Poon, Prof. Xi-Ren Cao, Prof. H. Vincent Poor, Prof. Junshan Zhang and Prof. Zhisheng Niu gave talks, respectively. Our group, Mr. Shiyong Yang and Yang Cao also attended the workshop. </text> 
<time> 2010-07-09</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Junshan Zhang visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 8-9, 2010, Prof. Junshan Zhang from Arizona State University visited our laboratory. He joined our group meeting and gave many useful suggestions for our research. </text> 
<time> 2010-07-08</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Xiaodong Wang visited our lab </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 3-5, 2010, Prof. Xiaodong Wang from Columbia Unviersity visited our lab. Prof. Xiaodong Wang gave a wonderful talk “Group Decoding for Interference Channels”. Then, he joined our group meeting and gave us many valuable suggestions.  </text> 
<time> 2010-07-03</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Qian Zhang visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 17-20, 2010, Prof. Qian Zhang from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology visited our laboratory. Prof. Qian Zhang gave many useful suggestions for our research. </text> 
<time> 2010-06-17</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> Prof. Zixiang Xiong visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On April 24-27, 2010, Prof. Zixiang Xiong from Texas A&amp;M University (USA), our lab.He joined our group meeting. At the meeting, we discussed our related work, which benefited us a lot. And he gave a wonderful talk "New results in quadratic Gaussian multiterminal source coding". </text> 
<time> 2010-04-24</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Chunming Qiao visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> Prof. Chunming Qiao who is from SUNY Buffalo visited our laboratory since April 6, 2010, and gave us two wonderful talks on: Cooperative Communication and Cloud Computing. Especially, he introduced the new research progresses of 4G mobile communications. Moreover, he joined our team meeting sometimes.  </text> 
<time> 2010-04-06</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Dr. Hai Jiang gave a talk</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On December 19-21, 2009, Dr. Hai Jiang from University of Alberta (Canada) visited our lab. He gave a wonderful talk "Optimal Multi-Channel Cooperative Sensing in Cognitive Radio Networks".  </text> 
<time> 2009-12-19</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> Prof. Jiang visited Zhejiang University </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> From August 30 to September 3, 2009, Prof. Jiang was invited by NESC Research Group to visit Zhejiang University. </text> 
<time> 2009-08-30</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Youwen Yi went to HKUST to study further</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 15, 2009, Youwen Yi went to HKUST for further study. </text> 
<time> 2009-07-15</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Shuguang Cui visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On July 6-27, 2009, Prof. Shuguang Cui from Texas A&amp;M University (USA) visited our lab. He gave a wonderful talk "Beamforming optimization for a two-way relay channel via SDP relaxation". </text> 
<time> 2009-07-06</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Dr. Guosheng Cheng visited our lab </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On May 4-5, 2009, Dr. Guosheng Cheng from Suzhou Institute of Nano-tech and Nano-Bionics visited our lab. Dr. Guosheng Cheng gave a talk “Electronic Properties of Single Semiconductor Nanowires”. We had a deep discussion with Dr. Guosheng Cheng on the Nano-network. </text> 
<time> 2009-05-04</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Dr. Xiangming Li visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On May 1-4, 2009, Dr. Xiangming Li from Beijing Institute of Technology visited our lab. He gave a wonderful talk "Fountain codes, Low-density parity-check codes and Network coding".  </text> 
<time> 2009-05-01</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Prof. Qian Zhang visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On April 12-16, 2009, Prof. Qian Zhang from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology visited our laboratory. She gave a wonderful talk "Cooperation in Cognitive Radio Networks".  </text> 
<time> 2009-04-12</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Sherman Shen visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On April 2-7, 2009, IEEE Fellow Prof. Sherman Shen from University of Waterloo, Canada visited our lab.</text> 
<time> 2009-04-02</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Dr. Yiyan Wu visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On March 3-7, 2009, IEEE Fellow Dr. Yiyan Wu from Communications Research Centre Canada visited our lab. </text> 
<time> 2009-03-03</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Jiang and Dr. Qu visited Sinano </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On December 13-15, 2008, Dr. Guosheng Cheng invited Prof. Jiang and Dr. Qu visited Sinano. Please find more details on website. http://cheng.sinano.ac.cn/cn/shown.asp?id=2</text> 
<time> 2008-12-13</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Dr. Jiang visited University of Colorado </title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> From July to September, 2008, Prof. Youjian Liu from University of Colorado at Boulder invited Dr. Jiang visited University of Colorado at Boulder as FULL visiting professor. </text> 
<time> 2008-07-10</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title> Prof. Qian Zhang visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 29-30, 2008, Prof. Qian Zhang from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology visited our lab. She gave a wonderful talk "Cognitive and Cooperative Wireless Networking". </text> 
<time> 2008-06-30</time> 
</news>



<news> 
<title> Dr. Yiyan Wu visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text>  On June 24-26, 2008, IEEE Fellow Dr. Yiyan Wu from Communications Research Centre Canada visited HUST. Dr. Yiyan Wu gave a wonderful talk “Broadband Multimedia in the Home”. </text> 
<time> 2008-06-24</time> 
</news>

<news> 
<title> Prof. Junshan Zhang and Shuguang Cui visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 2-3, 2008, Prof. Junshan Zhang from Arizona State University (USA) and Prof. Shuguang Cui from Texas A&amp;M University (USA) visited our laboratory. Prof. Junshan Zhang gave a wonderful talk " Threshold Structure of Channel Aware Distributed Scheduling in Ad-Hoc Networks: An Optimal Stopping Perspective". And Prof. Shuguang Cui gave a wonderful talk "Scaling Laws of Overlaid Cognitive Radio Networks".</text> 
<time> 2008-06-02</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title>Prof. Xiang-Gen Xiang visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On June 1-2, 2008, Prof. Xianggen Xiang from University of Delaware (USA) visited our lab. Prof. Xianggen Xiang gave a wonderful talk "Space-Time Coding/Modulation for MIMO Systems: What Is Left?". </text>
<time> 2008-06-01</time> 
</news>


<news> 
<title>Prof. Vijay K. Bhargava visited our lab</title> 
<image>  </image> 
<text> On November 10-13, 2007, Prof. Vijay K. Bhargava from University of British Columbia (Canada) visited HUST. rof. Vijay K. Bhargava gave a wonderful talk "Research Challenges in Cognitive Wireless Communication Networks". </text> 
<time> 2007-11-10</time> 
</news>


</newsList>